♪
Hmm.
[JINWOO]
Two of three ingredients done.
So all that's left...
is the purified blood
of the demon monarch.
Gotta be on my A-game
when I finally go for it.
The Demon's Castle definitely
helped me farm XP.
But officially,
I'm still stuck at E-rank.
So, how am I gonna be able to
participate
in higher-level raids.
[sighs]
I need to stop faking.
Not like
I can hide the truth forever.
[inhales]
It's time I retook
the hunter evaluation.
♪
[FEMALE ASSOCIATE 1A] If you
came for a rank assessment,
the line will form over here.
[KICHUL]
What kind of capable personnel
are we gonna recruit today?
He looks like a C,
and he's pretty obviously an E.
Who else we got?
[gasps]
[phone rings]
[BAEK]
Hello, Baek speaking.
[KICHUL] This is Kichul
from the second admin team!
Everything okay?
[KICHUL]
He just walked in!
He? D'you mean Sung?
Unless I'm dreaming, yes, sir!
And from the looks of it,
he's here
to get his hunter rank
reassessed!
-Right this way, please.
-Thank you.
If you're sure,
then I'm on my way.
[HUNTER CANDIDATE 16A] No need
to be nervous about this.
It's a simple test,
and not like you
can study for it.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm just trying to get
my ex-wife and daughter
to come back home, you know?
Need to get
this hunter stuff sorted out
so I can earn some cash.
-See those suits?
-Uh.
[HUNTER CANDIDATE 16A]
If you get ranked D or higher,
the scouts will approach you
and try to convince you
to join their guild.
[indistinct chatter]
So, don't worry.
As long as you aren't E,
you'll make a decent living.
[JINWOO]
"As long as you aren't E," huh.
[FEMALE ASSOCIATE 1A]
Next candidate!
Uh, coming.
Could you confirm
your name for me, please?
Jinwoo Sung.
-It's a reassessment, then.
-Yes.
It's the exact same process
you went through the last time
you were here.
Place your hand against
the black crystal and wait.
[alarm beeping]
Hold on. An error?
I'm sorry, could you try again?
[JINWOO]
Sure.
[alarm beeping]
That is so weird.
-Hey, what's wrong?
-Uh.
Hey, chief.
Something's not right.
I'm trying to assess him,
but it says, "error."
[JUNG]
Huh. Let me take a look at it.
One sec.
[alarm beeping]
Yep, it's the same every time.
-[exhales]
-What now?
Well, it isn't an error per se.
What it means is
he can't be assessed.
[FEMALE ASSOCIATE 1A]
Huh? I'm confused.
His mana levels
are so incredibly high
that they can't even be
measured by our equipment.
[gasps]
In other words.
[JUNG]
Yes.
He's the tenth person ever
in our country
to be an S-rank.
[CHOI] Any updates
on the winged ant situation?
[WOO]
The necropsy is underway.
The intel department
will compare the ant's biology
and its
"trace magic power levels"
with unwinged examples.
But it'll be a little longer
before I have
any results to report.
And so it goes.
Lots of strange things
keeping you all busy
like that red gate,
for instance.
Hmm.
It was a White Tiger raid
that some outsider
got to join, right?
And said outsider
defeated the dungeon boss.
But who is he?
[WOO] Though I was present
for the investigation,
I didn't see it
from start to finish.
Meaning I don't have
all the details.
And so it goes.
Oh, look.
Seems there's some sort
of commotion in the lobby.
Most likely an awakened
who got assessed
and is making a fuss about it.
[WOO]
I'll check it out.
[CHOI]
I think I'll go with you.
That way I get
all the details myself.
♪
They couldn't assess that guy?
That's just nuts!
Are we all witnessing history
in the making here?
-[JUNG] I realize it's...
-[MALE SCOUT 1] I think we are.
[MALE SCOUT 2]
Not like it's unprecedented
It's happened nine other times.
-[MALE SCOUT 3]Only nine times.
-We should have a solution
-in three days...
-Which means the nation finally
-got its 10th S.
-Yeah, sure thing.
[KICHUL] Manager Ahn
was right on the money!
Gotta grab him
before anyone else!
Once you come back,
we'll sort it out
and get your license updated.
Is that okay?
-Whoa. Look, guys!
-Huh?
[indistinct chatter]
[KICHUL] It's Jong-in Choi,
the head of the Hunters Guild!
[JINWOO] He who stands
at the pinnacle of fire magic,
or, as most people know him,
the "ultimate weapon."
[inhales]
Basically, the opposite
of my old nickname.
Ah. That certainly
explains the excitement.
Why, hello there.
I'm Jong-in Choi
from the Hunters Guild.
Although,
perhaps you knew that.
I would hate
to make assumptions, however.
Have you chosen a guild yet?
-If not, we could discuss it.
-Sorry, I'm busy.
[gasps]
[MALE GUILD SCOUT 16H]
Oh! No way!
[MALE GUILD SCOUT 16I[
He shot down Guildmaster Choi?
Am I crazy?
When I introduced myself
I said I was Jong-in Choi
from the Hunters Guild,
didn't I?
Yes.
That did happen.
[CHOI]
Perhaps I came off as arrogant.
[WOO] You're becoming quite
the celebrity, Hunter Sung.
[CHOI] He was awfully silent
as he left, too.
[WOO]
Could be an assassin type.
[panting]
[CHOI]
What is he doing here?
President Baek!
[CHOI]
I see what's going on.
The White Tiger's HQ
is relatively close by,
yet he ran hard enough
to be short of breath.
[KICHUL] And when I tried
calling out to him...
[CHOI] That's how badly
he wanted to talk
to that man in person.
Ding, ding, ding.
I think I found the outsider
who cleared the red gate.
[gasps]
Jong-in.
Uh.
[BAEK] Of all the people
to catch wind of this.
[machine beeping]
[JINWOO] She looks like she
could wake up any minute.
[machine beeping]
[JINWOO] I'll find
the cure for you, Mom.
Promise.
[door slides shut]
[WOO]
Today, I realized
how blind I've been
this whole time.
Which is fairly ironic,
given my position.
Watching hunters
and punishing law breakers.
And I'm usually confident
my judgment is sound.
[JINWOO] Are you saying
I need surveillance?
[WOO] Not the same way
a criminal might.
The surveillance team handles
all hunter-related incidents,
since no one else can.
The problem is,
when dealing with S-ranks,
even we're powerless.
All that to say, there's
someone who'd like to meet you.
Hm?
[gasps]
Hello, young man.
Pleasure to meet you,
I'm Gunhee Go,
chairman of
the Hunter's Association.
First and foremost,
I'd like to congratulate
you on your S-rank.
[JINWOO]
What?
They said to return, but it's
all a formality at this point.
The instant your mana
measured off the charts,
you became S-rank
by definition.
Okay. Then why?
Why do the formal
reassessment, you mean?
Simple.
Call it something
of a grace period.
It allows us
to contact individuals
like yourself
before the guilds pounce.
Believe it or not,
the Association doesn't have
many skilled hunters
on staff despite our reach.
There's no real way for us
to compete with the fame
and fortune on offer
from the larger guilds.
Manager Woo here
is among the most
elite members we have,
and even he's only A-rank.
Which brings me
to why I'm here tonight.
I'd be thrilled to call you
one of us, Hunter Sung.
Naturally,
you'll be given a position
of respect and authority
from day one.
[JINWOO]
Why go so far?
[GO GUNHEE]
Our nation's greatest advocates
are not politicians,
but hunters,
for we guard against
the threat of magic beasts.
At our core
are the prime defenders.
The five largest guilds.
Presently, there is
a delicate balance
between these five dragons.
Should you join one of them,
the balance will tip,
causing a substantial shift.
That said, the Association
also plays a vital role
as deterrent, the sixth dragon
keeping the others in check.
And you need muscle.
You do have
the strength for the job,
I can tell you that.
And perhaps even one day...
Are you interested?
[JINWOO]
It is a good offer.
A job at the Association
is basically
a guaranteed career.
I doubt there's anyone
who has greater influence
than Chairman Go,
especially with news outlets
and the government.
And, he's an amazing hunter.
Our country's
first ever S-rank.
His magic power is ridiculous,
you'd never guess he's over 80,
not with that physique.
He may be retired from hunting,
but I can feel he's still
as strong as I am,
even with
all my efforts to level up.
If I accept his offer,
my whole life will change.
Your thoughts, Hunter Sung?
I'm sorry, sir.
I have to decline.
[gasps]
[GO GUNHEE] It
comes down to money after all.
Because I want to fight.
To fight.
Fight against magic beasts,
you mean?
Yes.
I'm certain that the dungeons
are where I belong.
[GO GUNHEE] [gasps]
Remarkable.
I can see in his eyes
he's not lying.
How many years has it been,
since I felt this way?
I'm impressed my heart
still stirs such emotion in me.
If I were 20,
or even 10 years younger,
I could fight alongside
someone like him.
Hm.
I suppose that's fair.
I won't press the issue.
[JINWOO]
My sister's home alone,
so I'd better get going, sir.
It's been an honor.
[GO GUNHEE] Thank you,
and thank you for your time.
When I aged past the point
an S-rank healer
could counteract my decline,
I'd never felt
so crestfallen, before.
But now...
[chuckles]
clear my schedule for tonight.
I'd like to savor this feeling.
Say, Jinchul, would you care
to join me for a drink or two?
[WOO] I'll go but not partake,
if that's all right with you.
Suit yourself.
I wonder if he enjoys
a good drink?
[JINWOO] The Association mostly
handles D and E-rank dungeons.
Those aren't gonna
help me level up,
and mom's cure depends on that.
I'll keep fighting
and I won't stop.
Because I know
I can get even stronger.
[sirens wailing]
♪
[Hwang grunts]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[HWANG] Deputy Chief,
come to rub salt in my wounds?
They're still fresh.
[DEPUTY CHIEF 15A]
I just have a question
I want you to answer.
You've experienced
this Il-Hwan Sung's power.
Is he a beast,
or is he actually a human?
Did he look like a human
from where you stood?
Sure as hell seemed
like a beast to me.
Hmm.
All right.
Focus on your recovery, then
drop by the command center
once you're discharged
so you can file some paperwork.
What happened to him?
Unsure,
but we're on the lookout.
That said,
I doubt we'll be able
to bring in somebody who landed
you in a hospital bed.
♪
[grunts]
Shit!
You'd better stay the hell
away from my family.
Because if you try something,
even death won't be enough
to save you from me.
[voice echoing]
Save you from me.
[HWANG]
What a humiliating loss.
Even death won't save me?
[scoffs]
Is that his idea of a threat?
I know where he's headed.
I just need gear.
An artifact that'll let me
crush that bastard!
[JINWOO]
Artifacts,
usually some kind
of man-made relics.
But in the world of hunters,
they're high-level gear
that even seasoned craftsmen
can't create.
With the increase in hunters,
you're gonna find artifacts
online in auctions,
like anything else.
Why they gotta be
so expensive, though?
Uh!
I want my gear to be flawless
when I take on the last floors
of the castle.
Nothing in the system shop
seems right.
Could probably
sell the Sphere of Avarice.
It can be transferred.
Most of the best gear
in circulation
gives a 20% to 30%
boost in performance.
And since this thing
doubles magic damage,
it could double
its price tag, too.
Which would make one wonder
how an E-rank came to have him.
Might catch
some unwanted attention.
I'd look less suspicious
if I had a record
of going in A-rank gates,
but until my license
gets updated,
that won't be happening.
Oh! Or maybe it will.
[GO GUNHEE]
This was taken four years ago?
He looks quite different
and a great deal younger.
Think he falsified his rank?
Hmm.
His record states
that he's been severely injured
on several occasions.
So it's unlikely.
Four years of hell,
but he didn't give up.
The more I hear,
the more amazed I am.
He was paying
for his mother's treatment
and his younger sister's
tuition, it seems.
I suspect that's why he never
withdrew from hunting.
[GO GUNHEE] You don't often
see that kind of devotion
from young people these days.
There's a recent note as well.
He just signed up
to join a raid
with the Hunters Guild.
[GO GUNHEE]
Then what he said was all talk.
That big signing bonus
was too enticing.
[WOO]
Not necessarily.
According to the report, he's
on the excavation team, sir.
-He's mining?
-Yes.
Hm.
[chuckles]
Certainly likes to keep you
guessing, doesn't he?
[BAE]
You said you're E-rank?
-Yes.
-You mined before?
[JINWOO]
Eh, not exclusively.
[BAE]
Ah, a combat type.
You'll meet the fitness
requirement, no problem.
Well, good.
Got plenty of folks here
just like you who joined up.
Relax, work hard,
and let's get that bag!
-[chuckles]
-Right.
[JINWOO] Big raids
in high-rank dungeons
demand specialized teams.
The strike team
deals with magic beasts,
the mining team
digs up the mana crystals,
and the collection team
recovers the carcasses.
Damn, that's a lot of people,
but, for the profit.
And somewhere
in there, right now.
[shadow beast growling]
Such a travesty.
They don't seem to appreciate
the beauty of light.
♪
[fire roaring]
[smirks]
[beast growling]
Take position, tanks.
There's a storm coming.
♪
[CHOI] A well-done
carcass isn't much use,
so I tried to cook them
to a nice medium.
I believe that
took care of most
of our immediate enemies.
Let's continue on, shall we?
Oh, and sorry
for the burning smell,
I know one of you has
an especially sensitive nose.
[MALE WORKER 16A]
The strike team's coming out!
[JINWOO] They killed everything
but the dungeon boss already?
I could sense he was strong
the moment we met yesterday.
But for the entire squad
to come out unscathed,
goes to show just how strong.
All right.
After the second-in-command
comes out,
that should be everyone.
[JINWOO]
That's her.
The Vice Guildmaster
of the Hunters Guild,
and the country's
ninth S-rank to awaken.
Hae-in Cha, the Dancer.
Incredible.
Gotta wonder how many people
in the world
have a strong aura like that.
♪
Hm.
[CHA] I just
sensed something incredible.
A strong aura, like Chairman Go
was here for a second.
Well, whatever it was,
it's completely gone now.
Ugh!
[JINWOO] She's even sharper
than I thought.
[BAE]
Okay, people! We're goin' in!
[JINWOO]
Now, they rest while we work.
And there's no time limit since
the boss was saved for last.
One, two!
[MALE WORKER 16E]
Hey, chief! It's lookin' loose!
[clanking]
[JINWOO]
I can sense intense magic power
coming from that direction.
That's obviously
an A-rank dungeon boss.
Feels stronger
than the castle's
Vulcan and Metus,
that's for sure.
It's tempting.
I could go find out how tough
an A-rank boss really is.
[MALE WORKER 16F]
Did you hear?
The guy who just joined
on this job is an E-rank.
[MALE WORKER 16G]
E? You're kidding.
[MALE WORKER 16H] What the hell
was the boss thinking?
[indistinct chatter]
[JINWOO]
No matter where an E-rank goes,
the welcome
never gets any warmer.
Not that I'll be
doing this much longer.
-Oh.
-I'm workin' here!
And it's tight enough as it is
without idiots like you
standin' around
and blocking the way!
[gasps]
But, please, don't rush.
We're making great time
already. Go team!
[sighs]
Sheesh.
[LEE]
No way that guy's E-rank.
[MOK]
Uh, Chief?
I'm having some doubts
about the new recruit's rank.
Yeah?
[MOK]
Isn't he kinda strong for an E?
[BAE]
His ID says otherwise.
The way I see it, Sung here
is God's gift
to blue-collars like us.
[alarm blaring]
[BAE]
Break time, you guys!
Let's all go
get something to eat.
Breaks also apply to you,
Mister Sung!
I'm just gonna
finish up here first.
Don't overdo it.
And don't go too far
into the caves
or you might wind up
with the boss.
You got it.
[clanking]
Finally, they're gone!
Can't let this chance
slip by me.
Got an hour
till break's over, so...
Let's take a peek.
♪
Here we are, the boss chamber.
Yeah, that guy's definitely
stronger than Metus.
So much as I want to,
I know I shouldn't kill it.
The gate will close if I do,
and the Hunters Guild
will suffer a massive loss.
But, a little poke can't hurt.
[CHA] What exactly
do you think you're doing?
♪
I asked you a question.
It shouldn't be
that difficult to answer.
♪